{
	"cards": [
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-1",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"stop the ambulance and confront the driver.",
					"slow down and allow the driver to pass you.",
					"increase your speed to create more distance.",
					"slam on the brakes to frighten the tailgater."
				],
				"question": "When being tailgated by another vehicle while responding to an emergency call, you should:",
				"source": "See Defensive Ambulance Driving Techniques"
			},
			"back": "slow down and allow the driver to pass you."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-2",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"disinfection.",
					"sterilization.",
					"high-level disinfection.",
					"cleaning."
				],
				"question": "The process of removing dirt, dust, blood, or other visible contaminants from a surface or equipment is called:",
				"source": "See Phases of an Ambulance Call"
			},
			"back": "cleaning."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-3",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"hold a minimum capacity of 1,500 L of oxygen.",
					"undergo hydrostatic testing on a weekly basis.",
					"be capable of delivering oxygen at 1 to 15 L/min.",
					"be easily identifiable by their bright green color."
				],
				"question": "Regardless of where portable and mounted oxygen cylinders are stored in the ambulance, they must:",
				"source": "See Phases of an Ambulance Call"
			},
			"back": "be capable of delivering oxygen at 1 to 15 L/min."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-4",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"transferring the patient to the ambulance.",
					"emergency care provided at the scene.",
					"checking equipment on the ambulance.",
					"transport of the patient to the hospital."
				],
				"question": "Phases of an ambulance call include all of the following activities, except:",
				"source": "See Phases of an Ambulance Call"
			},
			"back": "emergency care provided at the scene."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-5",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"completing a detailed written report.",
					"restocking any disposable items you used.",
					"giving a verbal report to the triage clerk.",
					"informing the dispatcher of your arrival."
				],
				"question": "Delivering a patient to the hospital involves all of the following activities, except:",
				"source": "See Phases of an Ambulance Call"
			},
			"back": "giving a verbal report to the triage clerk."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-6",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"remain in the extreme right-hand lane.",
					"pass other drivers on the right side.",
					"remain in the extreme left-hand lane.",
					"drive in the center lane of the highway."
				],
				"question": "When driving an ambulance on a multilane highway in emergency mode, you should:",
				"source": "See Defensive Ambulance Driving Techniques"
			},
			"back": "remain in the extreme left-hand lane."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-7",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"stop signs.",
					"stop lights.",
					"intersections.",
					"railroad crossings."
				],
				"question": "The most common and usually the most serious ambulance crashes occur at:",
				"source": "See Defensive Ambulance Driving Techniques"
			},
			"back": "intersections."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-8",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"I",
					"II",
					"IV",
					"III"
				],
				"question": "A type _____ ambulance features a conventional, truck cab-chassis with a modular ambulance body that can be transferred to a newer chassis as needed.",
				"source": "See Emergency Vehicle Design"
			},
			"back": "I"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-9",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"an EMT and an AEMT.",
					"at least one EMT.",
					"an EMT and a paramedic.",
					"at least two EMTs."
				],
				"question": "Minimum staffing in the patient compartment of a basic life support (BLS) ambulance includes:",
				"source": "See Phases of an Ambulance Call"
			},
			"back": "at least one EMT."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-10",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Emergency childbirth kit",
					"Long bone splinting device",
					"Bleeding control supplies",
					"Stethoscope and penlight"
				],
				"question": "Other than personal safety equipment, which of the following should be the most readily accessible item in the back of an ambulance?",
				"source": "See Phases of an Ambulance Call"
			},
			"back": "Bleeding control supplies"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-11",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"a positive attitude about the ability to tolerate other drivers.",
					"realizing that lights and siren will be effective traffic tools.",
					"the ability to operate an ambulance at a high rate of speed.",
					"an offensive attitude about driving during an emergency call."
				],
				"question": "Characteristics of a safe ambulance operator include:",
				"source": "See Defensive Ambulance Driving Techniques"
			},
			"back": "a positive attitude about the ability to tolerate other drivers."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-12",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"park downhill from the scene.",
					"ask the driver to exit the vehicle.",
					"position the ambulance upwind.",
					"quickly gain access to the patient."
				],
				"question": "When arriving at the scene of an overturned tractor-trailer rig, you note that a green cloud is being emitted from the crashed vehicle. The driver is still in the truck; he is conscious but bleeding profusely from the head. After notifying the hazardous materials team, you should:",
				"source": "See Phases of an Ambulance Call"
			},
			"back": "position the ambulance upwind."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-13",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"120 and 140 mph.",
					"100 and 120 mph.",
					"150 and 200 mph.",
					"130 and 150 mph."
				],
				"question": "Typically, medevac helicopters fly at speeds between:",
				"source": "See Air Medical Operations"
			},
			"back": "130 and 150 mph."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-14",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"If the patient is stable, you may use the warning lights without the siren.",
					"If it is necessary to use the siren, you should tell the patient beforehand.",
					"Warning lights and siren should be avoided, even if the patient is unstable.",
					"It is generally acceptable to increase your speed if lights and siren are in use."
				],
				"question": "Which of the following statements regarding the use of the warning lights and siren on the ambulance is correct?",
				"source": "See Defensive Ambulance Driving Techniques"
			},
			"back": "If it is necessary to use the siren, you should tell the patient beforehand."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-15",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"pass the bus only after all the children have exited.",
					"slowly and carefully pass the bus on the left side.",
					"stop and wait until the warning lights stop flashing.",
					"back up and take an alternate route to the scene."
				],
				"question": "While en route to a call for a patient in cardiac arrest, you approach a stopped school bus with its red warning lights flashing. You should:",
				"source": "See Defensive Ambulance Driving Techniques"
			},
			"back": "stop and wait until the warning lights stop flashing."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-16",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"complete the run form before arrival at the hospital.",
					"converse with the patient and provide reassurance.",
					"reassess the patient only if he or she deteriorates.",
					"reassess unstable patients at least every 15 minutes."
				],
				"question": "During the transport phase of an ambulance call, it is most important to:",
				"source": "See Phases of an Ambulance Call"
			},
			"back": "converse with the patient and provide reassurance."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-17",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"contain anything that you might need during the first 5 minutes of patient care.",
					"facilitate defibrillation within 5 to 10 minutes after making patient contact.",
					"carry advanced life support equipment approved by the EMS medical director.",
					"manage a critically injured patient until he or she is loaded into the ambulance."
				],
				"question": "The purpose of a jump kit is to:",
				"source": "See Phases of an Ambulance Call"
			},
			"back": "contain anything that you might need during the first 5 minutes of patient care."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-18",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"400",
					"100",
					"200",
					"300"
				],
				"question": "Portable and mounted suction units must be powerful enough to generate a vacuum of at least ____ mm Hg when the tubing is clamped.",
				"source": "See Phases of an Ambulance Call"
			},
			"back": "300"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-19",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"turnout gear.",
					"safety goggles.",
					"face shields.",
					"hazardous materials gear."
				],
				"question": "Common safety equipment carried on the ambulance includes all of the following, except:",
				"source": "See Phases of an Ambulance Call"
			},
			"back": "hazardous materials gear."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-multiple-choice-card-20",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"30",
					"20",
					"10",
					"15"
				],
				"question": "Hydroplaning of the ambulance on wet roads would most likely occur at speeds of greater than _____ mph.",
				"source": "See Defensive Ambulance Driving Techniques"
			},
			"back": "30"
		}
	],
	"category": {
		"value": "chapter-38",
		"label": "Chapter 38"
	},
	"tags": [
		{
			"value": "multiple-choice",
			"label": "Multiple Choice"
		}
	]
}